[
    {
        "Quiz question": "What year was the first motor race held that was classed as Formula 1?",
        "Answer": "1950"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many stories did each of the World trade Towers Have?",
        "Answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the BBC how many rooms are there in Buckingham Palace?",
        "Answer": "775"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were the Orkney Islands reannexed to Scotaland from Norway",
        "Answer": "1472"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did brothers Richard and Maurice McDonald open their first McDonalds restaurant in San Bernardino, California?",
        "Answer": "1940"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The spanish Eurovision entry in 1986 entitled La La La contained how many la's?",
        "Answer": "138"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the pirate radio Radio Caroline launched?",
        "Answer": "1964"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many years in prison did the 12 members of the Great Train Robbery gang get between them in 1964?",
        "Answer": "307"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the Cutty Sark built?",
        "Answer": "1869"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Pablo Picasso die?",
        "Answer": "1973"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How long, in kilometres, is the Suez Canal?",
        "Answer": "163"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Pinky and Perky first appear on television?",
        "Answer": "1957"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the film Chitty Chitty Bang Bang released?",
        "Answer": "1968"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Madame Tussaud's first open?",
        "Answer": "1928"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Rio de Janeiro cease to be the capital of Brazil?",
        "Answer": "1960"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the country of Siam renamed Thailand?",
        "Answer": "1939"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first colour supplement to a Sunday newspaper appear?",
        "Answer": "1962"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first hot air balloon flight?",
        "Answer": "1783"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was DNA discovered?",
        "Answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the hot air balloon invented?",
        "Answer": "1783"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was NATO formed?",
        "Answer": "1949"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the television invented?",
        "Answer": "1926"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the National Health Service founded?",
        "Answer": "1948"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Ladislao Biro invent the ballpoint pen?",
        "Answer": "1946"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did MPs first receive a salary?",
        "Answer": "1911"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was the emergency number '999' introduced in the UK?",
        "Answer": "June 30th 1937"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Fletcher Christian lead the mutiny on the Bounty?",
        "Answer": "1789"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the world famous AGA cooker range invented?",
        "Answer": "1922"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the movie 'The Goonies' what year is on One-Eyed Willy's pirate treasure map?",
        "Answer": "1632"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was the old age pension introduced in Britain?",
        "Answer": "1909"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many muscles does a cat have in each ear?",
        "Answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Is it possible for a man in Scotland to wed his widows sister?",
        "Answer": "No (as he is dead)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On what date was Mickey Mouse born?",
        "Answer": "November 18 1928"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many times are the words 'Love Shack' mentioned in the B-52s hit of the same name?",
        "Answer": "40"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Travis song 'Sing', how many times is the word 'Sing' sung?",
        "Answer": "42"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How tall in feet is Salisbury Cathedral's spire from ground to tip?",
        "Answer": "404 feet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the numbering of houses first introduced?",
        "Answer": "1463"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was volleyball invented?",
        "Answer": "1895"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 1st, 2000, how many Popes have been assassinated?",
        "Answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first execution by lethal injection take place in America?",
        "Answer": "1982"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year were the Samaritans founded?",
        "Answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many days is the average gestation period of a mouse?",
        "Answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was the Barbie doll first sold with bendable legs?",
        "Answer": "1965"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the world record official attendance at the 1950 soccer world cup final?",
        "Answer": "199,854"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the famous 50 foot tall Hollywood sign first erected?",
        "Answer": "1923"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The first book of crosswords was published in what year?",
        "Answer": "1924"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did BBC 2 become the first British channel to broadcast in colour?",
        "Answer": "1967"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were professional soccer matches played on a Sunday in Britain for the first time?",
        "Answer": "1974"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When did the weather forecast appear in The Times newspaper for the first time?",
        "Answer": "1860"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By how many days did Amundsen beat Scott to become the first person to reach the South Pole?",
        "Answer": "35"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was barbed wire invented?",
        "Answer": "1874"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the British 2001 census what was the resident population of Scotland?",
        "Answer": "5,062,011"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did George de Mestral invent Velcro?",
        "Answer": "1955"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was the game of Monopoly invented?",
        "Answer": "1932"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many feature films did Alfred Hitchcock direct which had only one word in the title?",
        "Answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "To what speed does the car in 'Back To The Future' have to reach to travel in time?",
        "Answer": "88 miles per hour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Samuel Pepys make the first entry in his famous diary?",
        "Answer": "1660"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was the first Tour De France bike race contested?",
        "Answer": "1903"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Fairview is the most common name for a city in America. How many cities are named this?",
        "Answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the Irish political party, Sinn Fein formed?",
        "Answer": "1905"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Alexander Graham Bell invent the telephone?",
        "Answer": "1876"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first Christmas card produced?",
        "Answer": "1846"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Clarence Birdseye first put quick-frozen fish on sale?",
        "Answer": "1924"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the typewriter invented?",
        "Answer": "1829"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were the Grammy awards first awarded?",
        "Answer": "1959"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did trams first appear in London?",
        "Answer": "1861"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The first ever jukebox was installed at the Palais Royal Hotel in San Francisco in what year?",
        "Answer": "1899"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was Oxford University founded?",
        "Answer": "1167"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Alabama become the first American state to recognise Christmas as an official holiday?",
        "Answer": "1836"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first traveller's cheque cashed?",
        "Answer": "1772 (introduced by London Credit Company and could be used in 90 cities)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the company Microsoft founded?",
        "Answer": "1975"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the corkscrew patented?",
        "Answer": "1860"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What time did Paula Radcliffe record in the 2002 Chicago marathon when she set a new world record?",
        "Answer": "02:17:18"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the safety pin invented?",
        "Answer": "1849"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the planet Neptune discovered?",
        "Answer": "1846"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Sir Frederick Banting and J.J.R. MacLeod discover insulin?",
        "Answer": "1922"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Butlin's first holiday camp opened in Skegness in what year?",
        "Answer": "1935"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first English translation of the Bible completed?",
        "Answer": "1388"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were the Academy Awards for film first televised?",
        "Answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many storeys high is Sears Tower in America?",
        "Answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When the Great Train Robber Ronnie Biggs arrived back in England in 2001, how many days had he been on the run?",
        "Answer": "13,068"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many verses are there in the Bible?",
        "Answer": "30,334"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many islands are in Fiji?",
        "Answer": "332"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film starring Tom Hanks, what is Forrest Gump's I.Q.?",
        "Answer": "75"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Samuel Pepys write his last diary entry?",
        "Answer": "1669"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the BBC first broadcast opera on the radio?",
        "Answer": "1923"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first issue of the comic 'The Beano' published?",
        "Answer": "1938"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Dirty Dancing' was set in the summer of which year?",
        "Answer": "1963"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How tall is the Eiffel Tower in metres?",
        "Answer": "322"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the TV show 'Dr Who' first broadcast?",
        "Answer": "1963"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the Agatha Christie play 'Mousetrap' open in London?",
        "Answer": "1952"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was cricketer Bob Willis born?",
        "Answer": "1949"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the comic strip character of Popeye created?",
        "Answer": "1929"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many years elapsed between the Wright brothers' first flight and Neil Armstrong's walk on the Moon?",
        "Answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the British Library, the largest reference library in the UK, founded?",
        "Answer": "1753"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the Ryder Cup golf tournament launched?",
        "Answer": "1927"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did it become compulsory to wear seat belts in the front seat of a car?",
        "Answer": "1983"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the year 1900, what was the average age at death of people in America?",
        "Answer": "47"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were the first Nobel prizes awarded?",
        "Answer": "1901"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Morse code devised?",
        "Answer": "1832"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the telescope invented?",
        "Answer": "1608"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Fry's Turkish Delight first introduced?",
        "Answer": "1915"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first Cannes Film Festival held?",
        "Answer": "1946"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the highest UK chart position of Travis' single 'Why Does It Always Rain On Me'?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many light years away is the star Alpha Centauri from Earth?",
        "Answer": "4.28 light years"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The escalator installed in Britain was in the department store Harrods in what year?",
        "Answer": "1878"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did London's first airport open?",
        "Answer": "1919"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was Albert Einstein born?",
        "Answer": "1879"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Coca Cola first sold in bottles?",
        "Answer": "1894"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many white five pointed stars are there on the Brazilian flag?",
        "Answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were the Queensberry Rules, which apply to the sport of boxing, originally drawn up?",
        "Answer": "1867"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many league goals did Ally McCoist score for Rangers between the years 1985 and 1998?",
        "Answer": "355"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the first London marathon run?",
        "Answer": "1981"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Walt Disney born?",
        "Answer": "1901"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many steps are there in the Eiffel Tower?",
        "Answer": "1,792"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many miles long is the river Nile?",
        "Answer": "4160"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first women's golf tournament held?",
        "Answer": "1811"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many UK number one singles has Cliff Richard had?",
        "Answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many top 5 hits did Madonna have in the UK in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the first Alcoholics Anonymous first meeting take place?",
        "Answer": "1935"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Coca Cola introduce Cherry Coke?",
        "Answer": "1985"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Norwegian Johan Vaaler patent the paper clip?",
        "Answer": "1901"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the Empire State Building open?",
        "Answer": "1931"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Percy L. Spencer invent the microwave?",
        "Answer": "1947"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the country Ceylon renamed to Sri Lanka?",
        "Answer": "1972"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was Burger King founded?",
        "Answer": "1954"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Sweden become the first European country to issue bank notes?",
        "Answer": "1661"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many league goals has Ian Wright scored for Arsenal?",
        "Answer": "185"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was 'Nosferatu', the first vampire film released?",
        "Answer": "1922"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the first electric iron patented by H.W. Seely?",
        "Answer": "1882"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first cricket Test match take place between Australia and England?",
        "Answer": "1877"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When did the first successful parachute jump take place?",
        "Answer": "1797"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the year 1998, how many patents were registered in the United Kingdom?",
        "Answer": "43,181"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For how many years did Louis XIV of France reign?",
        "Answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first British Open Golf Championship held?",
        "Answer": "1860"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was Isaac Newton born?",
        "Answer": "1642"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was a test cricket match tied for the first time?",
        "Answer": "1960"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first bikini go on show at a Paris fashion show?",
        "Answer": "1946"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many steps are there to the top of the Eiffel Tower?",
        "Answer": "1792"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many miles long is the Mississippi river?",
        "Answer": "3860"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the film studio Paramount opened?",
        "Answer": "1912"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the notorious witch hunts take place in Salem in Massachusetts?",
        "Answer": "1692"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did American John D Rockefeller become the world's first billionaire?",
        "Answer": "1916"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the novel 'Robinson Crusoe' first published?",
        "Answer": "1719"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In kilometres, what is the circumference of the Earth's equator?",
        "Answer": "40,076km"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Mickey Mouse become 70 years old?",
        "Answer": "1998"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many films did Elvis Presley star in?",
        "Answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first FA Cup final held at Wembley?",
        "Answer": "1923"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Tesco, Sainsbury's, Safeway, Asda and Gateway first open on a Sunday?",
        "Answer": "1991"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many countries took place in the 1996 Olympic Games?",
        "Answer": "197"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did J Fletcher-Dodd found the first holiday camp?",
        "Answer": "1906"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was Napolean proclaimed emperor of France?",
        "Answer": "1804"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first parachute jump take place?",
        "Answer": "1783"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year were bar codes first introduced into shops in America?",
        "Answer": "1974"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many events were contested in the first ever Olympic Games?",
        "Answer": "43"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Income Tax introduced into the UK?",
        "Answer": "1799"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the last public execution by guillotine take place in France?",
        "Answer": "1939"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did William Gillette invent the safety razor?",
        "Answer": "1895"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Robert Rusticoat publish 'The Wasp', the first comic book ever to be published?",
        "Answer": "1802"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many islands make up the Maldives?",
        "Answer": "1196"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In kilometres, how long is the Suez Canal?",
        "Answer": "161.9 km"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first traffic light installed?",
        "Answer": "1868 (in England)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Pocahontas die?",
        "Answer": "1617"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first American test-tube baby born?",
        "Answer": "1983"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was Benny Goodman born?",
        "Answer": "1909"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Mensa founded?",
        "Answer": "1946"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When was Lewis Carroll's book 'Alice's Adventures in Wonderland' written?",
        "Answer": "1865"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did James Boyd patent the rubber fire hose?",
        "Answer": "1821"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Dick Whittington become Mayor of London?",
        "Answer": "1397"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first Miss World contest held?",
        "Answer": "1951"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the Davis Cup tennis competition first held?",
        "Answer": "1900"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did white lines first appear on Britains roads?",
        "Answer": "1925"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Jackie Stewart first win the Formula One World Drivers Championship?",
        "Answer": "1969"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the end of 2000, how many films has Harrison Ford appeared in which have earned over 100 million dollars worldwide?",
        "Answer": "16"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Buddy Holly when he died in a plane crash in 1959?",
        "Answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In football, in which year was the charity shield first contested for?",
        "Answer": "1908"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first charity Christmas card produced?",
        "Answer": "1949"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first recorded railroad accident occur?",
        "Answer": "1832"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many people signed the American Declaration Of Independence?",
        "Answer": "56"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The largest ever teddy bears picnic was held in Dublin in 1995. How many bears were there?",
        "Answer": "33,573"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the world's first daily newspaper published?",
        "Answer": "1702"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The TV series 'Planet Of The Apes' starring Roddy McDowell was set in what year?",
        "Answer": "3085"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was highwayman Dick Turpin hanged?",
        "Answer": "1739"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In BBC's 2002 100 Greatest Britons, which position was Robbie Williams?",
        "Answer": "77"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the London Underground begin operations?",
        "Answer": "1863"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In millimetres, what is the width of an A10 sheet of paper?",
        "Answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Arthur Conan Doyle publish the first of his 'Adventures Of Sherlock Holmes'?",
        "Answer": "1891"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In miles per hour, what is the land speed record on the moon as at 1st January 2000?",
        "Answer": "10.56 miles per hour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first American test-tube baby born?",
        "Answer": "1983"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year B.C. was Alexander the Great born?",
        "Answer": "356 BC"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year is the 1982 film Blade Runner set?",
        "Answer": "2019"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the radio show 'The Archers' begin?",
        "Answer": "1950"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Edmond Halley discover Halleys comet?",
        "Answer": "1682"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the character of Mickey Mouse first appear?",
        "Answer": "1928"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did London Zoo open?",
        "Answer": "1828"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Bartolomeo Cristofori event the piano?",
        "Answer": "1710"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How much did the USA pay Russia for Alaskan territory in 1867?",
        "Answer": "$7,200,000"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to his fake ID, in 'The Simpsons', in feet and inches how tall is Bart Simpson?",
        "Answer": "4 foot, 2 inches"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Leonardo Da Vinci design the first parachute?",
        "Answer": "1480"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the first postage stamp go on sale in Great Britain?",
        "Answer": "1840"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Nicholas Hillyard become the first ever to be granted a patent, when he did so for engraving and printing the King's head on documents?",
        "Answer": "1617"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the Polaroid camera invented?",
        "Answer": "1947"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did American Express introduce travellers cheques?",
        "Answer": "1891"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the atomic number of the element Californium?",
        "Answer": "98"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was 'Match Of The Day' first broadcast on BBC1?",
        "Answer": "1964"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the first commercial radio broadcast take place?",
        "Answer": "1920"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Alanson Crane patent the fire extinguisher?",
        "Answer": "1863"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did the Queen visit the Vatican for the first time?",
        "Answer": "1980"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year were electric christmas tree lights first used?",
        "Answer": "1895"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first women's cricket World Cup held?",
        "Answer": "1988"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many times is the 'F-word' used in the film 'Goodfellas'?",
        "Answer": "246"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Superman appeared for the first time in Issue of Action Comics. What was the year?",
        "Answer": "1938"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did India gain independence from the United Kingdom?",
        "Answer": "1947"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In feet, how high is Ben Nevis?",
        "Answer": "4,406 ft"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the Collins Millenium Dictionary, in what year was the word 'Allergy' introduced into the English language?",
        "Answer": "1907"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many times is the f-word used in the film 'Scarface'?",
        "Answer": "206"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Hungarian Professor Rubik invent his famous cube?",
        "Answer": "1975"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was the first penalty scored in an FA Cup final?",
        "Answer": "1910"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Walt Disney born?",
        "Answer": "1901"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Henry III when he became King in 1216?",
        "Answer": "9"
    }
]